101cargames.com 2011-12-28

# Play Car Games on 101CarGames.com - Privacy Policy

101cargames.com is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. We respect the privacy concerns of visitors to 101cargames.com. 

**Information we collect and how we use it**

On your visit to our website there is certain information that we collect from traffic references of hosting servers and from cookies. 

From traffic references of hosting servers - every time you visit a website, there is certain information you make available for collection such as IP address, time of visit, location, internet domain, type of browser and operating system used to access our site, pages you visit, if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website etc . We, like other operators, collect this information and use it for visitors' statistics and to improve our services to you. 

From Cookies - the sole purpose of cookies is to enhance your online experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by Web sites. Through your Web browser, cookies are only used by the Web site that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from 101cargames.com is only accessible by the 101cargames.com Web site. This information enables us to run our affiliate programs, allows customized advertising, lets you automatically sign in when you visit 101cargames.com, and offers other operational site activities. Most of browsers are set to accept cookies. But if you prefer, you can reset your browser so as to let you know whenever you receive a cookie or even to refuse cookies. However, you should know that some parts of 101cargames.com website can only be normally seen if your browser allows cookies. 

101cargames.com will not share your information with anyone. The only exception shall be in the event that disclosure of information is required by law enforcement or other government officials in connection with investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or that may expose you or us to legal liability. 

**Collection of information and Third-Party sites and Sponsors**

It is important that you understand that advertisers or Web sites that link to a site may collect personal information about you. The Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of other advertisers or Web sites. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our sites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other sites in order to help them provide relevant ads to users. Third parties may also be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on our website. If you do not wish for these third-parties to place and read cookies you can set your browser to block them. 

**ValueClick Media**

Online behavioral advertising (“OBA”) and/or multi-site advertising is occurring on 101cargames.com 

You can learn more about VCM by visiting their website: valueclickmedia.com

You can opt out from ValueClick or Network Advertising sites as follows: 

<https://admin.valueclickmedia.com/optout/index.html>

**Security**

All data that we collect is stored on one or more database servers. We are taking any reasonable precaution to secure the data, but you have to understand that the internet is not 100% safe and we cannot guarantee the safety of your information. All this kind of transmission whatsoever is made on your own risk. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Our website has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. 

**AGREEMENT WITH 101cargames.com POLICIES**

By using this site, you signify your assent to the 101cargames.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use 101cargames.com site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our web site to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices.
